prelaunchx.com 2012-10-04

# prelaunchX

Privacy Policy 

In order to offer this service, prelaunchX (PLX) collects and uses certain information about our users. This privacy policy outlines what information we collect, how we use that information and the controls we have put in place for you to protect your privacy. 

Information we collect 

**Personal Information.** When you sign up for PLX, or at some point as you use our service, we may ask you to provide some or all of the following information: 

  * a username of your choice
  * a password of your choice
  * your email address
  * your name
  * your physical address

**Other Information.** As you use our service, we may collect the following types of information: 

  * Internet protocol (IP) address
  * browser type
  * browser language
  * the date and time of your visit
  * the referring URL
  * unique anonymous identifiers in cookies
  * an identifier for the person who invited or referred you to PLX

How we use information we collect 

We use the information we collect to operate the PLX service. We use it to track the growth of your launch group. We also use it to help make sure you get paid when you qualify for earnings. 

A cookie containing a unique, anonymous identifier may be used to help keep track of your session as you use the PLX website. This allows our website to recognize your browser each time you load a page after you have logged in. 

PLX may use non-personal information—such as IP address, browser type, browser language, date and time of visit, etc.—to better understand usage patterns. This can help us to improve the service. This information may be stored or passed in cookies or pixel tags. 

Information we share 

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of PLX unless one of the following applies: 

  * **With your consent...**

This primarily refers to launches. When you participate in a launch, you are giving PLX express permission to share your name, physical address and email address with the website or service that is launching. This allows the launching website or service to make payment directly to you. 

  * **For legal reasons...**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of PLX if we have a good-faith belief that sharing such information is reasonably necessary to: 

    * comply with any applicable law, or enforceable government request.
    * detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud or security issues.
    * protect the rights, property or safety of PLX, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

Your controls 

You can change or update your personal information at any time by logging into your account and making those changes within the account control panel. The information we collect is essential to the way the PLX service operates. Therefore, the only way to remove all of your information from our systems is to terminate your account. Account termination is an option you will find within the account control panel. 

Sign up for PLX today and invite a few friends. It's quick, free and easy to join. Plus, it's fun to watch your launch group grow! 

You were invited by PLX user: jorgefop
